<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>HSK more content</name>
	<author>arpomo6</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>arpomo6.hmc.project</packageId>
	<description>
(ENG)
Version 0.51.
this mod do:
- add new weapons and ammo (EMP-ammo included too!);
- add a new traits (some of them may be dangerous!);
- add ammo-unmaking (the game won't get any easier!);
- add new dangerous factions (be ready!);
- and more...
P.S. This modification can cause a some butthurt, feelings of hatred, anger, or severe depression.
It is strongly not recommended for particularly nervous or impressionable persons. Persons who do not accept gaming inequality in any of its manifestations, as well as for childrens, pregnant persons and retirees.

Some weapon, ammo and armour textures was taken from other mods (Gun Nut, Project Itzal, [SY4] Vanilla-Friendly Weapon Pack, dianne's defaults - Weapons, Combat Extended Guns Retextured, Eccentric Tech - Foxy's Armory, Girls' frontline Weapon Pack, EVA Core, Not Only just a cannon, Vanilla XCOM Laser Weapons, ADE Advanced Turrets, AFU Cosmetic Gene Expanded, Horns and Ears and Things, DA Cosmetic Genes, Vanilla Animals Expanded, Cybernetic Warfare and Special Weapons and other old mods whose names I don't remember anymore unfortunately) and belong to their creators, some was taken from other games, some was made by me.

(RUS)
Версия 0.51.
Этот мод:
- добавляет новое оружие и боеприпасы (ЭМИ-боеприпасы в том числе!);
- добавляет новые черты характера (некоторые из них могут быть опасны!);
- добавляет разбор боеприпасов (игра от этого легче не станет!);
- добавляет новые опасные фракции (приготовьтесь!);
- и ещё кое-что...
P.S. Данная модификация может вызвать жжение в области заднего прохода, чувство ненависти, злости или вызвать сильную депрессию.
Настоятельно не рекомендуется для игры особо нервным или впечатлительным лицам. Лицам, не приемлющих игровое неравенство в любом его проявлении, а также детям, беременным и пенсионерам.

Некоторая часть текстур оружия, патронов и брони были взяты из других модов (Gun Nut, Project Itzal, [SY4] Vanilla-Friendly Weapon Pack, dianne's defaults - Weapons, Combat Extended Guns Retextured, Eccentric Tech - Foxy's Armory, Girls' frontline Weapon Pack, EVA Core, Not Only just a cannon, Vanilla XCOM Laser Weapons, ADE Advanced Turrets, AFU Cosmetic Gene Expanded, Horns and Ears and Things, DA Cosmetic Genes, Vanilla Animals Expanded, Cybernetic Warfare and Special Weapons и других старых модов, названия которых я уже не помню, к сожалению) и принадлежат их создателям, часть - из других игр, часть - сделана мною.
	</description>
	<url>https://boosty.to/arpomo6</url>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>experimental.optimizations</li>
		<li>dubwise.dubsperformanceanalyzer.steam</li>
		<li>DimonSever000.Wiki.Specific</li>
		<li>mlie.wikirim</li>
		<li>Taranchuk.PerformanceOptimizer</li>
		<li>notooshabby.rocketman</li>
		<li>Krkr.RocketMan</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>bs.performance</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
		<li>killface.facialstuff</li>
		<li>chjees.androids</li>
		<li>multilangcolorfultraits.pirateby</li>
		<li>telardo.BetterGeneGraphicsFramework</li>
		<li>HSK.WatcherContent</li>	<!-- some patches breaks iguf implants -->
		<li>HSK.Watcher.content.Fallout2</li>	<!-- just to be safe. Peka -->
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>arpomo6.hmc.ussrwp</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
