<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>HSK more content v0.26</name>
	<author>arpomo6</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.2</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<packageId>ArpoMo6.HMC.Project</packageId>
	<description>
(ENG)
It is very recommended not to disable the following modifications: multi lang colorful traits. HMC can work without its well, but some red errors can appears.
this mod do:
- add new weapons and ammo (EMP-ammo included too!);
- add a new traits (some of them may be dangerous!);
- add new Sharknado (why? because I can.);
- add ammo-unmaking (the game won't get any easier!);
- add new high-tech norbal and evilous drug-cat factions (be ready!);
- and more...
P.S. This modification can cause a some butthurt, feelings of hatred, anger, or severe depression.
It is strongly not recommended for particularly nervous or impressionable persons. Persons who do not accept gaming inequality in any of its manifestations, as well as for childrens, pregnant persons and retirees.

Some weapon, ammo and armour textures was taken from other mods (Gun Nut, Project Itzal, [SY4] Vanilla-Friendly Weapon Pack, dianne's defaults - Weapons, Combat Extended Guns Retextured, Eccentric Tech - Foxy's Armory, Girls' frontline Weapon Pack, EVA Core, Not Only just a cannon and other old mods whose names I don't remember anymore unfortunately) and belong to their creators, some was taken from other games, some was made by me.

(RUS)
Настоятельно рекомендуется не выключать следующие модификации: multi lang colorful traits. HMC может работать без них, но без них могут возникать некоторые ошибки.
Этот мод:
- добавляет новое оружие и боеприпасы (ЭМИ-боеприпасы в том числе!);
- добавляет новые черты характера (некоторые из них могут быть опасны!);
- добавляет Шаркнадо (why? because I can.);
- добавляет разбор боеприпасов (игра от этого легче не станет!);
- добавляет новые фракции хай-тек норбалов и злобных котиков с наркотиками (приготовьтесь!);
- и ещё кое-что...
P.S. Данная модификация может вызвать жжение в области заднего прохода, чувство ненависти, злости или вызвать сильную депрессию.
Настоятельно не рекомендуется для игры особо нервным или впечатлительным лицам. Лицам, не приемлющих игровое неравенство в любом его проявлении, а также детям, беременным и пенсионерам.

Некоторая часть текстур оружия, патронов и брони были взяты из других модов (Gun Nut, Project Itzal, [SY4] Vanilla-Friendly Weapon Pack, dianne's defaults - Weapons, Combat Extended Guns Retextured, Eccentric Tech - Foxy's Armory, Girls' frontline Weapon Pack, EVA Core, Not Only just a cannon и других старых модов, названия которых я уже не помню, к сожалению) и принадлежат их создателям, часть - из других игр, часть - сделана мною.
	</description>
	<modDependencies>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadBefore>
		<li>experimental.optimizations</li>
		<li>notooshabby.rocketman</li>
	</loadBefore>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>UnlimitedHugs.HugsLib</li>
		<li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
		<li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
		<li>killface.facialstuff</li>
		<li>chjees.androids</li>
		<li>multilangcolorfultraits.pirateby</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>ArpoMo6.HMC.USSRWP</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
